<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>GDG Bangalore</title>
    <description>Google Developer Group Bangalore</description>
    <link>http://kartikkannapur.github.io//GDG-Bangalore/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://kartikkannapur.github.io//GDG-Bangalore/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Google Cloud Workshop</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We organized a workshop on &lt;a href=&quot;https://cloud.google.com/&quot;&gt;Google Cloud&lt;/a&gt; inviting a bunch of people to give them a hands on experience on Google Cloud on the 7th of June 2014 in Hotel Royal Orchid, Bangalore.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://plus.google.com/u/0/+ShivamAgarwal404&quot;&gt;Shivam Agarwal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. How was your experience as a Speaker at Google Cloud Workshop?&lt;/strong&gt;
This was my first experience as a speaker in GDG event and I can simply describe it in one word - AWESOME!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. How was the response from the attendees?&lt;/strong&gt;
Attendees were a mixed crowd. One major problem I faced during the event was many attendees didn’t came prepared i.e. they didn’t had their machines preconfigured according to the instructions which were given earlier. This consumed some time during which more hands on experience was planned. One thing I liked about attendees was that they were very inquisitive. Their questions covered material which I was going to talk about in 4-5 slides ahead. This also created an atmosphere of curiosity to learn and think out of the box. Attendees from different careers and companies shared their experiences while asking questions, which helped in uncovering diverse application areas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. What you like the most during the event?&lt;/strong&gt;
Thing I like the most is the amount of energy, dedication and team work of GDG, GSA members to host the event successfully.I am very thankful to GDG Bangalore and Google to give me the opportunity of being a speaker. Thank you guys! GDG Bangalore rocks!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://plus.google.com/u/0/103302681672889679709&quot;&gt;Satendra Singh&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. How was your experience as a Speaker at Google Cloud Workshop?&lt;/strong&gt;
Its being great experience all together and got the opportunity to share knowledge and experience being a part of developer community of Google app engine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. How was the response from the attendees?&lt;/strong&gt;
The attendees asked quite technical question and variety of question being asked made the session more interesting and extensive exchange of knowledge about various challenges they are facing while implementing their solution on cloud and how Google app engine can solve their concern.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. What you like the most during the event?&lt;/strong&gt;
The most liked moment can be when attendees came forward and discuss their business problem to find the solution through Google app engine cloud platform and their willingness to know as much as possible.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2014 15:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://kartikkannapur.github.io//GDG-Bangalore/blog/Google-Cloud-Workshop</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kartikkannapur.github.io//GDG-Bangalore/blog/Google-Cloud-Workshop</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
